<gallery>
	<painting>
		<artist name="Vincent van Gogh">
			<image path="van_gogh.jpg" />
			<info>
				Vincent Willem van Gogh (30 March 1853 - 29 July 1890) was a
				Dutch Post-Impressionist painter who is among the most famous
				and influential figures in the history of Western art. In just
				over a decade he created approximately 2100 artworks, including
				around 860 oil paintings, most of them in the last two years of
				his life. They include landscapes, still lifes, portraits and
				self-portraits, and are characterised by bold, symbolic colours,
				and dramatic, impulsive and highly expressive brushwork that
				contributed to the foundations of modern art. Only one of his
				paintings was known by name to have been sold during his lifetime.
				Van Gogh became famous after his suicide at age 37, which followed
				years of poverty and mental illness.
			</info>
		</artist>

		<artist name="Leonardo Da Vinci">
			<image path="davinci.jpg" />
			<info>
				Leonardo di ser Piero da Vinci (15 April 1452 - 2 May 1519) was an
				Italian polymath of the High Renaissance who was active as a painter,
				draughtsman, engineer, scientist, theorist, sculptor, and architect.
				While his fame initially rested on his achievements as a painter, he
				has also become known for his notebooks, in which he made drawings and
				notes on a variety of subjects, including anatomy, astronomy, botany,
				cartography, painting, and paleontology. Leonardo is widely regarded to
				have been a genius who epitomized the Renaissance humanist ideal, and
				his collective works comprise a contribution to later generations of
				artists matched only by that of his younger contemporary Michelangelo.
			</info>
		</artist>

		<artist name="Michelangelo">
			<image path="michelangelo.jpg" />
			<info>
				Michelangelo di Lodovico Buonarroti Simoni (6 March 1475 - 18 February
				1564), known mononymously as Michelangelo, was an Italian sculptor,
				painter, architect, and poet of the High Renaissance. Born in the Republic
				of Florence, his work was inspired by models from classical antiquity and
				had a lasting influence on Western art. Michelangelo's creative abilities
				and mastery in a range of artistic arenas define him as an archetypal
				Renaissance man, along with his rival and elder contemporary, Leonardo da
				Vinci. Given the sheer volume of surviving correspondence, sketches, and
				reminiscences, Michelangelo is one of the best-documented artists of the 16th
				century. He was lauded by contemporary biographers as the most accomplished
				artist of his era.
			</info>
		</artist>

		<artist name="Raphael">
			<image path="raffaello.jpg" />
			<info>
				Raffaello Sanzio da Urbino (March 28 or April 6, 1483 - April 6, 1520), now
				generally known in English as Raphael, was an Italian painter and architect
				of the High Renaissance. His work is admired for its clarity of form, ease
				of composition, and visual achievement of the Neoplatonic ideal of human
				grandeur. Together with Leonardo da Vinci and Michelangelo, he forms the
				traditional trinity of great masters of that period.
			</info>
		</artist>

		<artist name="Rembrandt">
			<image path="rembrandt.jpg" />
			<info>
				Rembrandt Harmenszoon van Rijn (15 July 1606 - 4 October 1669), usually simply
				known as Rembrandt, was a Dutch Golden Age painter, printmaker, and draughtsman.
				An innovative and prolific master in three media,he is generally considered one
				of the greatest visual artists in the history of art. It is estimated Rembrandt
				produced a total of about three hundred paintings, three hundred etchings, and
				two thousand drawings.
			</info>
		</artist>

		<artist name="Claude Monet">
			<image path="monet.jpg" />
			<info>
				Oscar-Claude Monet (14 November 1840 - 5 December 1926) was a French painter and
				founder of impressionist painting who is seen as a key precursor to modernism,
				especially in his attempts to paint nature as he perceived it. During his long
				career, he was the most consistent and prolific practitioner of impressionism's
				philosophy of expressing one's perceptions before nature, especially as applied
				to plein air (outdoor) landscape painting. The term "Impressionism" is derived
				from the title of his painting Impression, soleil levant, exhibited in 1874
				(the "exhibition of rejects") initiated by Monet and his associates as an
				alternative to the Salon.
			</info>
		</artist>
	</painting>

	<music>
		<artist name="David Bowie">
			<image path="bowie.jpg" />
			<info>
				David Robert Jones (8 January 1947 - 10 January 2016), known
				professionally as David Bowie was an English singer, songwriter,
				musician, and actor. He is regarded as one of the most influential
				musicians of the 20th century. Bowie was acclaimed by critics and
				musicians, particularly for his innovative work during the 1970s.
				His career was marked by reinvention and visual presentation, and
				his music and stagecraft had a significant impact on popular music.
			</info>
		</artist>

		<artist name="Michael Jackson">
			<image path="michealjackson.jpg" />
			<info>
				Michael Joseph Jackson (August 29, 1958 - June 25, 2009) was an
				American singer, songwriter, dancer, and philanthropist. Known
				as the "King of Pop", he is regarded as one of the most significant
				cultural figures of the 20th century. During his four-decade career,
				his contributions to music, dance, and fashion, along with his
				publicized personal life, made him a global figure in popular culture.
				Jackson influenced artists across many music genres. Through stage and
				video performances, he popularized complicated street dance moves such
				as the moonwalk, which he named, as well as the robot.
			</info>
		</artist>

		<artist name="Eminem">
			<image path="eminem.jpg" />
			<info>
				Marshall Bruce Mathers III (born October 17, 1972), known professionally as
				Eminem is an American rapper. He is credited with popularizing hip hop in Middle
				America and is often regarded as one of the greatest rappers of all time. His
				global success and acclaimed works are widely regarded as having broken racial
				barriers for the acceptance of white rappers in popular music. While much of his
				transgressive work during the late 1990s and early 2000s made him a controversial
				figure, he came to be a representation of popular angst of the American underclass
				and has been cited as an influence by and upon many artists working in various genres.
			</info>
		</artist>

		<artist name="Lady Gaga">
			<image path="gaga.jpg" />
			<info>
				Stefani Joanne Angelina Germanotta (March 28, 1986), known professionally as Lady Gaga,
				is an American singer, songwriter, and actress. She is known for her image reinvention
				and versatility in the entertainment industry. Gaga began performing as a teenager,
				singing at open mic nights and acting in school plays. She studied at Collaborative Arts
				Project 21, through the New York University Tisch School of the Arts, before dropping out
				to pursue a career in music. After Def Jam Recordings canceled her contract, she worked
				as a songwriter for Sony/ATV Music Publishing, where she signed a joint deal with
				Interscope Records and KonLive Distribution, in 2007. Gaga had her breakthrough the
				following year with her debut studio album, The Fame, and its chart-topping singles
				"Just Dance" and "Poker Face". The album was later reissued to include the extended play
				The Fame Monster (2009), which yielded the successful singles "Bad Romance", "Telephone",
				and "Alejandro".
			</info>
		</artist>

		<artist name="Celine Dion">
			<image path="celinedion.jpg" />
			<info>
				Celine Marie Claudette Dion CC OQ (30 March 1968) is a Canadian singer. Referred to as the
				"Queen of Power Ballads", she is noted for her powerful and technically skilled vocals.
				Her music has incorporated genres such as pop, rock, R&amp;B, gospel, and classical music.
				Her recordings have been mainly in English and French, although she has also sung in
				Spanish, Italian, German, Latin, Japanese, and Chinese.
			</info>
		</artist>

		<artist name="Steve Perry">
			<image path="steveperry.jpg" />
			<info>
				Stephen Ray Perry (born January 22, 1949) is an American singer and songwriter. He wasthe
				lead singer and frontman of the rock band Journey during their most successful years from
				1977 to 1987, and again from 1995 to 1998. He also wrote/co-wrote several Journey hit
				songs. Perry had a successful solo career between the mid-1980s and mid-1990s, made sporadic
				appearances in the 2000s, and returned to music full-time in 2018.
			</info>
		</artist>
	</music>

	<movies>
		<movie name="The Terminator">
			<image path="terminator.jpg" />
			<info>
				The Terminator is a 1984 American science fiction action film directed
				by James Cameron. It stars Arnold Schwarzenegger as the Terminator, a
				cybernetic assassin sent back in time from 2029 to 1984 to kill Sarah
				Connor (Linda Hamilton), whose unborn son will one day save mankind from
				extinction by Skynet, a hostile artificial intelligence in a
				post-apocalyptic future. Kyle Reese (Michael Biehn) is a soldier sent back
				in time to protect Sarah. The screenplay is credited to Cameron and
				producer Gale Anne Hurd, while co-writer William Wisher Jr. received an
				"additional dialogue" credit.
			</info>
		</movie>

		<movie name="Oppenheimer">
			<image path="oppenheimer.jpg" />
			<info>
				Oppenheimer is a 2023 epic biographical thriller film written and directed
				by Christopher Nolan. It stars Cillian Murphy as J. Robert Oppenheimer, the
				American theoretical physicist credited with being the "father of the atomic
				bomb" for his role in the Manhattan Project—the World War II undertaking that
				developed the first nuclear weapons. Based on the 2005 biography American
				Prometheus by Kai Bird and Martin J. Sherwin, the film chronicles the career
				of Oppenheimer, with the story predominantly focusing on his studies, his direction
				of the Manhattan Project during World War II, and his eventual fall from grace
				due to his 1954 security hearing. The film also stars Emily Blunt as Oppenheimer's
				wife "Kitty", Matt Damon as head of the Manhattan Project Leslie Groves, Robert
				Downey Jr. as United States Atomic Energy Commission member Lewis Strauss, and
				Florence Pugh as Oppenheimer's communist lover Jean Tatlock. The ensemble supporting
				cast includes Josh Hartnett, Casey Affleck, Rami Malek, and Kenneth Branagh.
			</info>
		</movie>

		<movie name="Forrest Gump">
			<image path="gump.jpg" />
			<info>
				Forrest Gump is a 1994 American comedy-drama film directed by Robert Zemeckis and
				written by Eric Roth. It is based on the 1986 novel of the same name by Winston Groom
				and stars Tom Hanks, Robin Wright, Gary Sinise, Mykelti Williamson and Sally Field.
				The film follows several decades in the life of a slow-witted yet kindhearted Alabama
				man named Forrest Gump (Hanks) and his experiences in the 20th-century United States.
				The film differs substantially from the novel.
			</info>
		</movie>

		<movie name="Batman">
			<image path="batman.jpg" />
			<info>
				Batman is a 1989 superhero film based on the DC Comics character of the same name,
				created by Bob Kane and Bill Finger. Directed by Tim Burton, it is the first installment
				of Warner Bros.' initial Batman film series. The film was produced by Jon Peters and
				Peter Guber and stars Jack Nicholson, Michael Keaton, Kim Basinger, Robert Wuhl, Pat
				Hingle, Billy Dee Williams, Michael Gough, and Jack Palance. The film takes place early
				in the title character's war on crime and depicts his conflict with his archenemy The
				Joker.
			</info>
		</movie>

		<movie name="Joker">
			<image path="joker.jpg" />
			<info>
				Joker is a 2019 American psychological thriller film directed by Todd Phillips, who
				also co-wrote the screenplay with Scott Silver. The film, based on DC Comics characters,
				stars Joaquin Phoenix as Joker. Set in 1981, it follows Arthur Fleck, a failed clown and
				aspiring stand-up comic whose descent into mental illness and nihilism inspires a violent
				countercultural revolution against the wealthy in a decaying Gotham City. Robert De Niro,
				Zazie Beetz and Frances Conroy appear in supporting roles. Distributed by Warner Bros.
				Pictures, Joker was produced by Warner Bros. Pictures and DC Films in association with
				Village Roadshow Pictures, Bron Creative and Joint Effort.
			</info>
		</movie>

		<movie name="Gladiator">
			<image path="gladiator.jpg" />
			<info>
				Gladiator is a 2000 epic historical drama film directed by Ridley Scott and written
				by David Franzoni, John Logan, and William Nicholson. It was released by DreamWorks
				Pictures in North America, and Universal Pictures internationally through United
				International Pictures. It stars Russell Crowe, Joaquin Phoenix, Connie Nielsen,
				Tomas Arana, Ralf Möller, Oliver Reed (in his final role), Djimon Hounsou, Derek
				Jacobi, John Shrapnel, Richard Harris, and Tommy Flanagan. Crowe portrays Roman
				general Maximus Decimus Meridius, who is betrayed when Commodus, the ambitious son of
				Emperor Marcus Aurelius, murders his father and seizes the throne. Reduced to slavery,
				Maximus becomes a gladiator and rises through the ranks of the arena to avenge the
				murders of his family and his emperor.
			</info>
		</movie>
	</movies>
</gallery>